# SANAZ ZERAATI ABOUT ME

A self-taught front-end developer for a year and a mature person with more than 5 years of experience with an engineering background as a GIS technician and control project manager. During this time, I realized my interest in web development and decided to enter the profession resolutely as a front-end developer with a HackYourFuture course and other educational resources.

I am a highly enthused, responsible, motivated, hardworking, and reliable person. I have experience working as part of a team and individually and extremely driven, with a clear goal to succeed. Hence, I am keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills as a Front-End Developer in your company.

## **CONTACT**

- szeraati69@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/sanaz-zeraati
- github.com/sanaz-git
- +98 9140567100

## **LANGUAGE**

English (Advance) German (Basic) Persian (Native)

#### **SKILLS**

**HTML** 

CSS

**GIT** 

JavaScript

ReactJS

Python

R

**ARCGIS & QGIS** 

MS Project

Microsoft Office

Photoshop

# **ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS**

Hiking, Climbing, Traveling, Music

# TRAINING COURSE

#### HACKYOURFUTURE CURRICULUM

web development program

June 2021 - June 2022

- Ability to build a basic modern web application
- How to use third-party libraries/APIs
- Have a basic concept of what it means to work on digital products
- Learn about GIT and its basic usage
- Know the basic building blocks of JavaScript
- Understand what the Document Object Model (DOM) is
- Use the basics of DOM Manipulation
- Gain awareness of the inner workings of JavaScript
- · Learn what an Application Programming Interface (API) is
- Connect with different public APIs
- Build a Single Page Application (SPA)
- Understand the React way of thinking about user interfaces
- Know the importance and place of state and how to pass it down
- Be able to work with different lifecycle hooks
- Distinguish between class-based versus function-based components
- How to handle client-side routing

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### CONTROL PROJECT MANAGEMENT

## **Water & Waste Water Company**

September 2019 - Present

- I have been able to planning, overseeing and leading projects from ideation through to completion and Ensuring projects meet deadlines, Monitor project costs, feedback and reporting
- Optimise project strategies to achieve better results in the future.
   Spearheaded development of Standard Operating procedures

# **GIS SPECIALIST**

## Water & Waste Water Company

January 2017 - September 2019

- Deployed Web GIS abled company to save 60 percent of time and money for learning employees and provide them with less interest that allows them to access GIS data, edit attributes, add new features, etc. on any computer from anywhere there is an internet connection.
- Increase 50 percent speed in updating authoritative data in an enterprise geodatabase and Development of data management tools and scripts to retrieve data sources for production

# **EDUCATION**

## MASTER OF SCIENCE WATER RESOURCE ENGINEERING

Shahid Bahonar University of Kerman, Iran

September 2013 - September 2016

Operation Evaluation of Copula Function in Flood Frequency Analysis

# **BACHELOR OF WATER ENGINEERING**

Shahid Bahonar University of Kerman, Iran

September 2009- September 2013

Mapping underground Dam in Arid and Semi-Arid Area